<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-27T19:47:21+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">GUSEC</title><subtitle>Promoting Cyber Security at the University of Glasgow</subtitle><author><name>GUSEC</name></author><entry><title type="html">Meet The New Board</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/27/Meet-The-Board.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meet The New Board" /><published>2023-01-27T19:13:13+00:00</published><updated>2023-01-27T19:13:13+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/01/27/Meet-The-Board</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/27/Meet-The-Board.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello_world&quot;&gt;Hello_World&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re pleased to announce that today, after a period of dormancy, that GUSEC is back in buisiness! We’ve got loads of great stuff planned, so I hope you’re all as excited as we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are just joining us, we’ll give you a run down of our modus-operandi, then we’ll introduce ourselves so you can get to know us better ahead of all the upcoming activites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll probably lay said activities out in a different post, so watch out for that coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-you-can-expect-from-us&quot;&gt;What You Can Expect From Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re the Glasgow Unversity Cyber-Security Society, so you can expect to gain knowledge and insight into one  of the most saught-after career paths in the tech industry right now through talks, workshops, and socials. But not just that, we pride ourselves on being a welcoming and helpful community with shared values and interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the coming weeks and years, we hope to foster this community into something we can really be proud of and something that hopefully out-lasts our time in the university and gives you skills and friendships that outlasts yours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get a better understanding of how our society is going to operate from now on, check out the new &lt;a href=&quot;/files/constitution.pdf&quot;&gt;constitution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-we-expect-from-you&quot;&gt;What We Expect From You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The society is open to everyone, meaning that you don’t need to sweat it if you’re not technically confident. We do however require that you keep our society safe from bullying and harrassment, our rules and proceedures regarding these sorts of incidents are once again outlined in the &lt;a href=&quot;/files/constitution.pdf&quot;&gt;constitution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrapping-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping Up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way, all that’s left to say is that we hope you enjoy the coming weeks with us and we look forward to seeing you at our next event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The GUSEC team&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>GUSEC</name></author><summary type="html">Hello_World</summary></entry></feed>